<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Theo\'s stash</string>
    <string name="infinity_stones_title">Collect all infinity stones</string>
    <string name="single_stone_title">Stone title</string>
    <string name="stone_detail_quest_text">Quest Text</string>
    <string name="button_gather_stones">Gather the Infinity Stones !!!</string>
    <string name="menu_button">Gather infinity stones !</string>
    <string name="gather_button">Gather Infinity Stones !!!</string>
    <string name="agree_button">Whatever it takes !</string>


    <string name="power_stone_quest">
        \tI know strength is one on your main skills, but Evil in the galaxy much stronger than expected\.
        As a proof of your strength, possess Hulks power\.\n
        You need to push your body above the ground for a 100 of times,
        in limit of magic 30 minutes\.
        \n\n
        Avenger Hulk - Julio
    </string>
    <string name="time_stone_quest">
        \tFor the time of realizing your quest, you need the help of Ancient One to gather into your memories\.\n
        Show to the world your youngest appearance to fool enemies, which are on your way to hunt you down\.
                \n\n
        Avenger Ancient One - Julio
    </string>
    <string name="soul_stone_quest">
        \t To finish the quest, you need to reunion first with Almighty God of Thunder - Thor\.\n
        With the power of his powerful axe - Stormbreaker, you need to clear 30 anniversary challenge\.\n
        You need to achieve "3" -> "0"
                \n\n
        Avenger Hawkeye - Jordi

    </string>

    <string name="mind_stone_quest">
        This require an absolute mind knowledge. The password for this stone is within the riddle\.\n\n\n
        \"The poor people have me, the rich people want me\. If you eat me, you will die\"\.
         \n\n

    </string>
    <string name="space_stone_quest">
       You saw how Thor look now\.\.\. All because of the beer\. You need to travel through all universe
        to get him back, before he will collapse\.
        While in \"Meantime\" he will grab some beers
         \n\n
        Avenger Thor (the fat one) - Tomasz
    </string>
    <string name="reality_stone_quest">
        \tThis one is the toughest\.
        You need to collect all previous stones before reaching to this one\.\n
        All Avengers need to be with you, and combined power from all you will allow
        to gain the full potential of your work\.\n
        Gather together to recreate the song, as \"Earth, Wind and Fire\" used to sing:
        \"Do you remember, 21st night of September ?\"
          \n\n
        Avenger Black Widow - Tiziana
    </string>

    <string name="title_scroll_view">Hey Kid\.\.\.</string>

    <string name="story_scroll_view">
        \t
        If you read to this, it means that Dr. Strange story finished good and i understood why he didn\'t want to tell me how exactly it will finish.\n\n
        When we prepared to fight Thanos, i was aware that your 30 anniversary is soon. Some thoughts in my mind told me i need to prepare for that.\n\n
        While Avengers were busy planning the last battle, i used the Infinity Stones to hide the stash in secure place. \n\n

        As you might understand by this moment i want you to collect all of them to receive the ultimate stash.
        All of the data how to collect them is hidden is this phone.\n
        On purpose network connection is off, in case somebody might want to track you.\n
        I left you small hints to every single stone how they should be collected in your reality.\n\n
        Some of task are more challenging. That was the only way to be sure non other person will collect things which are waiting for you.\n\n
        To achieve the password to collect the stone, contact with the person your Avenger friend for a confirmation of the quest.
        \n\n
        So, will you do it? \n\n

        whatever it takes ? \.\.\.
    </string>

    <string name="power_stone_password">hulkwillsmash</string>
    <string name="time_stone_password">ihavecometobargain</string>
    <string name="soul_stone_password">iamstillworthy</string>
    <string name="mind_stone_password">nothing</string>
    <string name="space_stone_password">noobmaster69</string>
    <string name="reality_stone_password">avengersassemblehere</string>

    <string name="bday_wishes">
        That about it Theo, continue the Journey with your Avengers and Happy 30\'s\. Hope you enjoyed your quest\. The stash is yours, use is wisely\.
        \n\nI am proud of You\.
        \n\nHappy Birthday \!\!\!
    \n\n Let\'s the party begin \!
    </string>
    <string name="confirm_button">confirm</string>
    <string name="title_enter_password">Enter password AVENGER</string>


</resources>
